University Photograph; Collection ua390
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- A portrait of Mildred Graham, New York State Normal School, Class of 1889. The photograph is marked with "Veeder Albany, N.Y.", Undated
- Pictured are: Peggy Casey, New York State College for Teachers, Class of 1945, Bob Sullivan, New York State College for Teachers, Class of 1946, and Hal Weber, New York State College for Teachers, Class of 1947., Undated
- A group portrait including alumna Carrie (Caroline) H. Mayhew (second row, center), with Sarah E. Blaynerf, Ella J. McGucken, Mary Kavanagh, Nelly Moak, and Marie L. Sumers. Mayhew's name is handwritten at the top of the border surrounding the tintype., Undated
- A picture of Walter V. Barbish, New York State College for Teachers, Class of 1955., Undated
- A portrait of James L. Lockhart, New York State College for Teachers, Class of 1956. Lockhart worked for the United States Office of Education., Undated
- A portrait of Isabella K. Sharpe, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1963 and 1965., Undated
- A group portrait of members of the State University of New York at Albany Alumni Association, New Beginnings Chapter, Chicago, Illinois., Undated
- A group portrait of members from the New York State College for Teachers, Class of 1916 on the occasion of its 50th year reunion, State University of New York at Albany, Alumni Day, 1966. There are crop marks on all sides of the photograph., Undated
- A picture of Thomas C. Anderson, State University of New York at Albany faculty member in the School of Business, in his office., Undated
- An instructor with a student studying a human skeleton; perhaps the activity of an Anthropology or Biological Sciences class or lab., Undated
- A State University of New York at Albany unidentified professor with an unidentified student during a class meeting., Undated
- A STUDENT LOOKING AT SLIDES An unidentified student at the State University of New York at Albany reviewing slides with a projector., Undated
- An unidentified art student in the foreground at the State University of New York at Albany working with watercolors., Undated
- The proposed planetarium for the University at Albany., Undated
- Frank C. Jettner with a telescope on top of the State University of New York at Albany's earth science building., Undated
- An unidentified astronomer at the State University of New York at Albany displaying the revolution of the earth around the sun., Undated
- Paraboloid in the midst of being reassembled on the State Univeristy of New York at Albany's uptown campus., Undated
- Frank C. Jettner teaching a class in the atmosperhic sciences department at the State University of New York., Undated
- State University of New York at Albany professor, Joseph Erkes takes readings as he works on reassembling the radio telescope., Undated
- A contact sheet of images depicting action shots from games played by the State University of New York at Albany basketball team during the 1973-74 season., Undated
- A picture of basketball players during a game in the gymnasium. In the top margin is written "150%" and in the bottom margin is written "100%" and an illegible note that has been crossed out., Undated
- Mike Suprunowicz, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1977 shooting a basket during a game. In the bottom margin is written "3 3/4 x 6 7/8.", Undated
- A photograph of the State University of New York at Albany basketball team. Duplicate of 331., Undated
- A picture of cheerleaders leading a cheer at halftime during a basketball game., Undated
- A photograph of the 1922-1923 New York State College for Teachers men's basketball team. The emusification is torn in the upper right corner of the photograph. The bottom right corner is embossed with the letter "K.", Undated
- A picture of football players warming up for a practice session by performing stretching exercises. A member of the coaching staff is motivating them., Undated
- A picture of a State University of New York at Albany football player, about to pass the football. In the bottom margin is written "Dave Machson IM - SUNY 61.5%" and "108%" and "100%" both of which are crossed out., Undated
- A portrait of Joseph P. Rinaldo, football player for the State University of New York at Albany, 1973., Undated
- Three unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany football team., Undated
- A photograph of a scoreboard during a game in which the State University at Albany football team has 35 points. In the right margin is part of another photographic image., Undated
- Members of the State University of New York at Albany football team poseing for a picture during practice., Undated
- Frank Villanova, player on the State University of New York at Albany football team, in the process of falling to the ground., Undated
- The State University of New York at Albany football team and coaches., Undated
- A picture of an unidentified football coach advising a State University of New York at Albany football player during the Homecoming Game, 1977., Undated
- A picture of Carla B. Landsman, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1979 and member of the State University of New York at Albany gymnastics team. She is performing an exercise on the balance beam., Undated
- An unidentified member of the State University of New York at Albany gymnastics team performing on the uneven bars., Undated
- Headshot of Tom Cerra, former student of the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- Headshot of Pete Weykamp, former student of the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- Headshot of Jay Kianka, former student of the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- The State University of New York at Albany's men's lacrosse 1975-1976 team posing for a group shot on benches., Undated
- Members of the State University of New York at Albany's men's lacrosse team during a practice., Undated
- A headshot of Jerry Hardy, member of the State University of New York at Albany football team., Undated
- Portrait of Jay Kianka, State University of New York at Albany class of 1975., Undated
- An unidentified student of the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- An unidentified student of the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- An unidentified student of the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- Portrait of Roland Levie, a student at the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- A portrait of an unidentified football player and student at the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- Portrait of an unidentified student of the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- Gretchen Harig of the class of 1978 stands for a portrait with her softball mitt in hand., Undated
- Nancy Kowalsky of the class of 1978 stands for a portrait in the gymnasium., Undated
- The State University of New York at Albany's Women's softball team, in the front row from left to right are Terry Sakala, Judi Heitz, Sue Busher, Monica Sheehan, Jane Sper, and Marion Funosa. In the back row from left to right there is the assistant coach, Lynn Thompson, Mollie Cas, Patsy Titus, Paula Gizzi, Joan Pfuller, Barb Hale, Peggy Ross, and Coach Leona Rhenish., Undated
- Pat Malatestinic, State University of New York at Albany's class of 1978 and member of the Women's softball team., Undated
- Portrait of Carolyn DeVito, a student at the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- TEAM 1968-1969. DUPLICATE OF 5806. Spring of 1969, near the current softball field, on the bench that was our complete dugout. The visiting team also had a long bench. Coach is Claudette DeLamater who was our coach for the 1966, '67, '68, and '69 seasons. Seniors are: Donna Swart, and Linda Lintz(seated in the middle Swart wearing glasses, and Lintz is to her left.) Front: Susan Delmonte, Joanne Whalen, Mary Wimmer, Donna Swart, Linda Lintz, Linda Meyers, Ellen Gantwerk, Marie Michel Back: Gloria Mazure, Diane Taubold, ?, ?, Susan Tatro, Coach, ?, Joan Viskocil, Jo Vecchi, Dolores Boberski, Leslie King, Undated
- A picture of a diver having executed a dive from a springboard diving board above an indoor swimming pool., Undated
- Unidentified State University of New York at Albany swimmers, poised to dive into the pool and race., Undated
- An unidentified State University of New York at Albany diver, just as he breaks the surface of the water of an indoor swimming pool., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany's swim team about to enter the pool during a race., Undated
- An unidentified swimmer of the State University of New York at Albany's Women's swim team during a practice., Undated
- An unidentified swimmer of the State University of New York at Albany's Women's swim team during a practice., Undated
- An unidentified swimmer of the State University of New York at Albany's Women's swim team during a practice., Undated
- A portrait of the unidentified former swim coach for the State University of New York at Albany's Women's swim team., Undated
- A portrait of an unidentified member of the State University of New York at Albany's Women's swim team., Undated
- A portrait of an unidentified member of the State University of New York at Albany's Women's swim team., Undated
- A portrait of an unidentified member of the State University of New York at Albany's Women's swim team., Undated
- A portrait of an unidentified member of the State University of New York at Albany's Women's swim team., Undated
- A portrait of an unidentified member of the State University of New York at Albany's Women's swim team., Undated
- An unidentified member of the State University of New York at Albany's swim team diving into the pool., Undated
- An unidentified member of the State University of New York at Albany's Women's swim team exiting the pool., Undated
- An unidentified member of the State University of New York at Albany's swim team diving into the pool., Undated
- A team photograph of the State University of New York at Albany's Women's swim team., Undated
- An unidentified member of the State University of New York at Albany's swim team diving into the pool., Undated
- A team photograph of the State University of New York at Albany's Women's swim team., Undated
- A group portrait of the State University of New York at Albany's women's swim team., Undated
- Group shot of the State University of New York at Albany's Men's vollyball team., Undated
- Portrait of Rick Porter, student of the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- Portrait of John Alden, student of the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- Portrait of Jack D'Ambrosio, student of the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- A contact sheet with State University of New York at Albany's men's wrestling team participating in a meet., Undated
- A contact sheet with State University of New York at Albany's men's wrestling team participating in a meet., Undated
- A contact sheet with State University of New York at Albany's men's wrestling team participating in a meet., Undated
- A contact sheet with State University of New York at Albany's men's wrestling team participating in a meet., Undated
- Portrait of Walter Katz, student of the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- Portrait of Jeff Golden, student of the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- Portrait of Rod Williams, student of the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- Portrait of Jeff Aronowitz, student of the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- Portrait of Doug Bauer, student of the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- Portrait of Ken Knickmyre, student of the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- Portrait of Ethan Grossman, student of the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- Portrait of Vic Gagliardi, student of the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- Portrait of Larry Mims, student of the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- Portrait of Frank Herman, student of the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- Portrait of Rich Robbins, student of the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- Portrait of Jeff Golden, student of the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- Portrait of Rich Lawrence, student of the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- Portrait of Ken Knickmyre, student of the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- Portrait of Rudy Vido, student of the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- Portrait of Springer, student of the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- State University of New York at Albany tennis players in action on the court., Undated
- The State University of New York at Albany 1975 men's tennis team, from left to right, Steve Taylor, Dave Denny, Josh Cannel, Curt Samuels, Mitt Johnson, Bob Disken, Leo Strernlicht, John Weinberg, Joe Kestenbaum, and the coach Bob Lewis., Undated
- The exterior of the State University of New York at Albany's Atmosperic Sciences Research Center's solar energy house near the Schenectady Airport., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community., Undated
- An unidentified student working in the Mohawk Tower Weather Station on the campus of the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- Director of the ESSA Research lab, George S. Denton at the State University of New York at Albany's Weather Modification Conference., Undated
- Portrait of Verner E. Suomi at the State University of New York at Albany's Weather Modification Conference., Undated
- Portrait of W. Boynton Beckwith at the State University of New York at Albany's Weather Modification Conference., Undated
- LOUIS T. BENEZET,VOLKER MOHEN,VALERIY IVANOVICH OPOKON (SOVIET SCIENTIST),LOUIS R. SALKEVER,VALENTIN AUGUSTIVICH SHTEINBERG (SOVIET SCIENTIST),AND ALEXANDER DUNKEL, Undated
- Jane Kotvis Slack, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1970 and Chairman of the Athletic Association Board, receiving an award from Alfred C. Werner of the Department of Physical Education., Undated
- A portrait of Steve Bosak, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1975 and member of the baseball team, 1974., Undated
- Richard "Doc" Sauers coaching a State University of New York at Albany basketball game., Undated
- A photograph of the New York State College for Teachers' basketball team, 1921. "M.C. Wilhelus" is written on the reverse of the original., Undated
- A player on Oneonta's basketball team is mid-air, having either made a basket or blocked a shot., Undated
- Unidentified students walking toward and away from the Dutch Quadrangle at the State University of New York at Albany on the uptown campus. There are crop marks on all sides of the original., Undated
- Unidentified students in the formal garden behind the Campus Center at the State University of New York at Albany uptown campus. Written on the back is "DIVISION OF SOCIAL AND BEHAVIORAL SCIENCES." There are crop marks in the top, left, and bottom margins of the original., Undated
- An unidentified student of the State University of New York at Albany observing a slide through a microscope., Undated
- Three unidentified students of the State University of New York at Albany conducting a biology lab., Undated
- State University of New York at Albany, professor Samuel M. McGee-Russel conducting a lab experiment., Undated
- A portrait of State University of New York at Albany student, Joseph Tupper., Undated
- A picture of Ruth Bissell, New York State College for Teachers, Class of 1915, with her uncle. The picture is from Bissell's Class of 1915 album., Undated
- An unidentified State University of New York at Albany student playing the guitar by a body of water. There are crop marks in the right and bottom margins of the original. Written in the bottom margin is "A" and "C-9.", Undated
- A picture of Nicholas Thomas Brignola. Brignola was born July 17, 1936 in Troy, N.Y. and died Feb. 8, 2002 in Albany, N.Y. He was a trumpet player, a jazz saxophonist, and also played the clarinet and flute., Undated
- A portrait proof of Bertha Brimmer, member of the New York State Normal College, Class of 1900 and faculty member., Undated
- A portrait of Lillian C. Lowell, New York State Normal School, Class of 1888. In the bottom margin is the photographer's stamp, "Brown" and "Albany, N.Y." Written on the reverse is "Hawpe.", Undated
- Pictured are, left to right: Chuck Gordon, Nick Nealon, and Larry Brown. On the reverse is written "Friends.", Undated
- Exterior of the State University of New York at Albany's Sayles Hall on Alumni Quadrangle., Undated
- Postcard of Sayles Hall at the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- The front of Pierce Hall on Alumni Quadrangle. Duplicate of 3393., Undated
- The dining room of the New York State College for Teacher's Sayles Hall., Undated
- An unidentified dining room in at the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- An interior of an unidentified hall at the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- A collage of State University of New York at Albany photographs during an unidentified event., Undated
- A group of unidentified people, possibly students, buying and selling jewelry and t-shirts in the lobby of the Campus Center at the State University of New York at Albany. There are crop marks in the top and right margins. Written in the top margin is "Photo 1C" and between two arrows is written "29 picas." Written between two arrows in the right margin is "34p.", Undated
- An unidentified male, possibly a student, selling t-shirts bearing athletic company logos in the Campus Center Lobby at the State University of New York at Albany. There are crop marks in the top and right margins. Written in the top margin is "Photo 1B" and between two arrows is written "14 picas." Written between two arrows in the right margin is "14 picas." student selling t-shirts in the campus center, Undated
- An unidentified man selling jewely at a table in the lobby of the Campus Center at the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- View of the State University of New York at Albany's Uptown Campus from Dutch Quadrangle. Campus Center in foreground, State Quadrangle in background., Undated
- Unidentified people dining at the Patroon Room in the Campus Center at the State University of New York at Albany. The photo was taken from behind a potted plant, which can be seen in the foreground., Undated
- An unidentified student purchasing food from an employee of the Campus Center Cafeteria at the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- Two unidentified students standing outside of the campus center at the State University of New York at Albany on the uptown campus. One of the students is wearing a false nose., Undated
- A photograph of a portion of Clark's Wall in Campus Center Assemby Hall, designed and installed by A. William Clark of the Art Department at the State University of New York at Albany. There are crop marks in the top and left margins on the orginal., Undated
- An unidentified female student reading a newspaper in the Campus Center at the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- An unidentified student eating in the Campus Center cafeteria at the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- An unidentified student drinking a beverage and reading a newspaper at the snack bar in the Campus Center at the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- An unidentified student sitting on the Campus Center Terrace reading a book at the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- View from the Campus Center to the Education and Humaniities Buildings on the Uptown Campus., Undated
- Unidentified students entering the Campus Center through the entrance on the Academic Podium at the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- Unidentified students standing by the fountain outside of the Campus Center at the State University of New York at Albany on the uptown campus., Undated
- Unidentified students on the Campus Center Terrace at the State University of New York at Albany. There are crop marks in the right, bottom, and left margins of the original., Undated
- Two unidentified students talking by the small fountain by the Campus Center at the State University of New York at Albany uptown campus., Undated
- A group of unidentified students at an art vending stand outside of the of Campus Center at the University of New York at Albany., Undated
- Academic Podium with the Campus Center in the background on the Uptown Campus., Undated
- Unidentified students walking by the fountain outside of the Campus Center at the State University of New York at Albany uptown campus. There are crop marks in the top margin., Undated
- Aerial view of the State University of New York at Albany's Uptown Campus, looking west., Undated
- Winter scene of the Uptown Campus viewed from Indian Quadrangle., Undated
- Alice Kilts and Freida Krom, New York State College for Teachers, Class of 1921, standing near one of the buildings of the downtown campus., Undated
- The front of Van Derzee Hall on the State University of New York at Albany's Downtown Campus., Undated
- Unidentified students talking in a corridor of the State University of New York at Albany's Draper Hall., Undated
- A picture of Alumni Association members, mostly women, who are at a "Meeting of the alumni." Hawley Hall is in the background and Draper Hall is the building on the viewer's left -- both buildings are located on the downtown campus. Figures in the background appear to be men and they look to be in academic costume. There are crop marks on all sides of the photograph and in the left margin is written ".86 9A pg 7" with 9A enclosed in a circle., Undated
- State University of New York at Albany's Uptown Campus as viewed from the south., Undated
- View of the Uptown Campus at night. Duplicate of images 10343 and 10345., Undated
- A contact sheet displaying images of Senator Daniel Patrick Moynihan delivering a speech. Moynihan served in the U.S. Senate from New York as a Democrat from 1977-2001. The speech was delivered in the Performing Arts Center., Undated
- View of the Performing Arts Center from the Water Tower on the Uptown Campus., Undated
- Aerial view of the State University of New York at Albany's Uptown Campus looking south., Undated
- View of Sports Center from the Academic Podium on the Uptown Campus., Undated
- Front of Pierce Hall on Alumni Quadrangle. Duplicate of 3392., Undated
- Exterior of Pierce Hall on Alumni Quadrangle in winter., Undated
- A picture of an unidentified student sitting on a bench in front of the fountain on the Academic Podium of the State University of New York at Albany uptown campus., Undated
- A photograph of the Carillon Tower and one of the Quadrangles, possibly the State Quadrangle, still incomplete, in view. The original is mounted on a pice of matte board., Undated
- Night view of the Uptown Campus. Duplicate of images 10344 and 10345., Undated
- View of the Uptown Campus at night. Duplicate of 10343 and 10344., Undated
- The Carillon tower and the Campus Center at the State University of New York at Albany. There are crop marks on all sides of the original. Written in the top margin is "To 29 [square]s" between two arrows. Written between to arrows in the left margin is "TO 44 [square]s.", Undated
- Aerial view of the State University of New York at Albany's Uptown Campus looking south., Undated
- Formal gardens behind Campus Center., Undated
- Two unidentified students walking down stairs at the State University of New York at Albany on the uptown campus. The original is mounted on a piece of matte board and has crop marks in the right and bottom margins., Undated